<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Monikers</string>
    <!-- Facebook application ID and custom URL scheme (app ID prefixed by 'fb'). -->
    <string name="facebook_application_id" translatable="false">762029845495164</string>
    <string name="facebook_login_protocol_scheme" translatable="false">fb762029845495164</string>
    <!-- Twitter guess -->
    <string name="twitter_application_id" translatable="false">monikers-cee6a</string>
    <string name="twitter_login_protocol_scheme" translatable="false">twmonikers-cee6a</string>
    <string name="ndopen" translatable="false">Navigation Drawer Open</string>
    <string name="ndclose" translatable="false">Navigation Drawer Closed</string>

    <string name="Contact" translatable="false">We are students at Syracuse University\n
    Bryan Sweeney, Joanna Huiying Wu, and Matt Mawson (mmawson@syr.edu)</string>

    <string name="gameDescription" translatable="false">Monikers is a party game based on public domain game Celebrity.
        Two teams, comprised of two or more players each, come together for a minimum of
        four players. To start the game, any player can use their mobile phone and enter five monikers,
        which can be anyone or anything - real or fictitious.\n
        Once all players have entered their monikers, the app shuffles them and play proceeds in three rounds.
        In the first round, one player from the first team is designated to provide clues to their team
        to guess each moniker. The designated player has 60 seconds to read five monikers, one at a time,
        and provide clues without saying the name of the moniker. The second team plays after 60 seconds
        have elapsed. In the second round, the designated player is limited to providing a one-word clue.\n
        In the third round, the designated player has to pantomime the moniker using sounds and gestures
        but no words. The playing team can make as many guesses as they want. If they guess correctly,
        the designated player touches the “correct” button on the phone, and the team gets points. The
        team with the most points at the end of three rounds wins.</string>

    <string-array name="game_time_options">
        <item>1:00</item>
        <item>1:30</item>
        <item>2:00</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>